Leonard Everett Fisher Papers
© 2010 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Correspondence, undated, 1950-1999
  - Appearances, 1961-1999
    - NJEMA, Parsippany, NJ, 1996 October 22 (Box 87:642)
    - Ferguson Library, Stamford, CT, 1996 November 3 (Box 87:643)
    - Shore and Country Club, Norwalk, CT, 1996 November 7 (Box 87:644)
    - UCONN, Storrs, CT, 1996 November 16 (Box 87:645)
    - Green Farms Academy, Green Farms, CT, 1996 November 18 (Box 87:646)
    - Appearances, 1997 (Box 87:646A)
    - Appearances, 1998 (Box 87:646B)
    - Appearances, 1999 (Box 87:646C)
  - Cards, undated, 1990-1998
    - Birthday and Father's Day Cards, 1990s (Box 88:647A)
    - Holiday Cards, 1994 (Box 88:647)
    - Holiday Cards, 1995 (Box 88:648)
    - Holiday Cards, 1996-1998 (Box 88:649A)
    - Holiday Cards, undated (Box 88:649)
    - Oversized Valentine's Day card from Kati Higley, undated (Box 91:685)
  - Universities (Alphabetical), undated, 1963-1994
    - Miscellaneous Universities, undated (Box 89:650)
    - Miscellaneous Universities, 1982+ (Box 89:651)
    - Calvin College, 1994 (Box 89:652)
    - Fairfield University, 1983 (Box 89:653)
    - Fairfield University: course descriptions / rosters, 1983+ (Box 89:654)
    - Fairfield University: course outline and notes, 1985 Fall (Box 89:654A)
    - Fairfield University: course catalogs, undated (Box 89:655)
    - Ohio State University, 1983-1985 (Box 89:656)
    - Paier College of Art: memos, letters and cards, 1963+ (Box 89:657)
    - Paier College of Art: Resignation from Dean, 1982-1984 (Box 89:658)
    - Paier College of Art: Commencement information, 1982+ (Box 89:659)
    - Paier College of Art: course descriptions / syllabi, undated (Box 89:660)
    - Paier College of Art: instructor and course evaluations, 1982-1985 (Box 89:661)
    - Paier College of Art: Newsletters, 1979+ (Box 89:662)
    - Paier College of Art: Miscellaneous, 1977+ (Box 89:663)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1968+ (Box 89:664)
    - Rhode Island School of Design, 1977-1978 (Box 90:665)
    - Rutger's University, 1980+ (Box 90:666)
    - Sacred Heart University, 1976-1981 (Box 90:667)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, 1977+ (Box 90:668)
    - SUNY, 1971-1980 (Box 90:669)
    - University of Hartford, 1975+ (Box 90:670)
    - University of Connecticut, 1977+ (Box 90:671)
    - University of Minnesota, 1973+ (Box 90:672)
    - University of Oklahoma, 1987+ (Box 90:673)
    - University of Oregon, 1968-1974 (Box 90:674)
    - University of Southern Mississippi, 1973-1989 (Box 90:675)
    - Wright State University, 1975-1976 (Box 90:676)
    - Yale, 1975+ (Box 90:677)
- Series V: Exhibits: Programs, Correspondence / Appearance programs, 1946-1999
  - Invitations to exhibit, correspondence, etc., 1971+ (Box 92:1)
  - Marketing pamphlet for "Story Lines" exhibit, undated (Box 92:2)
  - "Story Lines" notes on illustrations for exhibit, undated (Box 92:3)
  - List of paintings etc., Arthur Brown & Bro. exhibit, 1951 October 9 (Box 92:4)
  - Program, Edwin Hewitt Gallery exhibit, 1952 February 11 (Box 92:5)
  - Correspondence, Trinity College, Hartford exhibit, 1952 November 29 (Box 92:6)
  - Children's Book show pamphlet, 1961-1962 (Box 92:7)
  - Program, announcements, correspondence, The Center Gallery, 1966 October 30 (Box 92:8)
  - Silvermine Guild of Artists, program, 1968 July 20 (Box 92:9)
  - The John Slade Ely Home, program, 1968 September 22 (Box 92:10)
  - "The Illustrators' Art" The Upstairs Gallery, program, 1968 November 20 (Box 92:11)
  - "Festival of Contemporary Religious Art" exhibit, program, 1969 March 26 (Box 92:12)
  - The Silvermine Guild of Artists exhibit, correspondence, 1969 April 5 (Box 92:13)
  - "6th Annual" New Haven Paint & Clay Club, program, 1969 April 7 (Box 92:14)
  - The Mid-Fairfield Country Youth Museum, program, 1969 April 11 (Box 92:15)
  - Penn State, media release, 1969 April 19 (Box 92:16)
  - "The First May Pageant of the Arts", invitation, 1969 May 2 (Box 92:17)
  - Washington Post Children's Book Fair, program, 1969 May 4 (Box 92:18)
  - The Silvermine Guild, program, correspondence, 1969 June 13 (Box 92:19)
  - The deGrummond Collection, pamphlets, 1970 (Box 92:20)
  - Westport, CT, poster, 1970 March 15 (Box 92:21)
  - The New Haven Paint & Clay Club, program, invitation, 1970 April 19 (Box 92:22)
  - Beaux Arts Ball Exhibit, correspondence, 1970 April 26 (Box 92:23)
  - The Mid-Fairfield CountyYouth Museum, program, 1970 May 1 (Box 92:24)
  - Appearance: NESLA, program, 1970 May 14 (Box 92:25)
  - Appearance: Children's Book Illustration, program, 1970 July 6 (Box 92:26)
  - The John Slade Ely House exhibit, program, 1970 October 11 (Box 92:27)
  - Gallery 86 exhibit, announcement, 1970 December 3 (Box 92:28)
  - "The USA at the Frankfurt Book Fair" exhibit, program, 1971 (Box 92:29)
  - "22nd New England Exhibit", program, 1971 (Box 92:30)
  - Appearance: The New Haven Jewish Center, program, 1971 (Box 92:31)
  - "Festival of Contemporary Religious Art"exhibit, program, 1971 April 1 (Box 92:32)
  - "Mainstreams '71" exhibit, program, 1971 April 4 (Box 92:33)
  - Mid-Fairfield County Youth Museum, correspondence, 1971 April 11 (Box 92:34)
  - New Haven Paint & Clay Club, invitation, program, 1971 April 25 (Box 92:35)
  - Mid-Fairfield County Youth Museum, program, 1971 October 22 (Box 92:36)
  - University of Bridgeport, invitation, 1972 April 8 (Box 92:37)
  - New Haven Paint & Clay Club, program, 1972 April 23 (Box 92:38)
  - Brass Ring Gallery, announcement, 1972 May 30 (Box 92:39)
  - The Butler Institute of American Art, program, invitation, 1972 July 2 (Box 92:40)
  - Fairfield University, poster, 1972 October 1 (Box 92:41)
  - The John Slade Ely House, program, invitation, 1972 Octobe 8 (Box 92:42)
  - "Twenty-four Years in Retrospect", correspondence, notes, 1973 February 4 (Box 93:43)
  - The Danbury Scott Museum, press release, newsletter, 1973 March (Box 93:44)
  - The John Slade Ely House, program, invitation, 1973 October (Box 93:45)
  - New Haven Paint & Clay Club, painting listing, 1973 October 7 (Box 93:46)
  - Fairfield University, announcement, 1973 October 18 (Box 93:47)
  - "Audubon Artists", program, 1974 (Box 93:48)
  - New Haven Paint & Clay Club, program and invitation, 1974 March 10 (Box 93:49)
  - Bloomindales exhibit, correspondence, invitation, etc., 1974 April 26 (Box 93:50)
  - Connecticut Festival of Arts & Crafts, invitation, program, 1974 May 11 (Box 93:51)
  - Community Cooperative Nursery School, invite, poster, etc., 1974 June 21 (Box 93:52)
  - Temple Israel exhibit, flyer, 1974 October (Box 93:53)
  - Weston High School, list of paintings, 1974 October 1 (Box 93:54)
  - The John Slade Ely House, program, 1974 October 6 (Box 93:55)
  - "7th Annual Art Festival", brochure, 1974 November 8 (Box 93:56)
  - Community Cooperative Nursery School, correspondence, 1975+ (Box 93:57)
  - Audubon Artists 33rd Annual", program, 1975 January 16 (Box 93:58)
  - Prism 76 ,"Bicentennial Posters", correspondence, invite, 1975 February 28 (Box 93:59)
  - "Heritage and Horizon", 1975 May 10 (Box 93:60)
  - Essex Art Association, program, 1975 August 2 (Box 93:61)
  - Essex Art Association, program, 1975 October 4 (Box 93:62)
  - The John Slade Ely House, invitation, program, 1975 October 12 (Box 93:63)
  - CPTV Gallery 24, program, article featuring, 1975 October 21 (Box 93:64)
  - Prism Gallery, program, invitation, 1975 October 24 (Box 93:65)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1976 (Box 93:66)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1977 (Box 93:67)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1978 (Box 93:68)
  - Correspondence for exhibits, 1979 (Box 93:69)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1979 (Box 93:70)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1980 (Box 93:71)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1981 (Box 94:72)
  - The Saltbox Gallery exhibit, invite, correspondence, 1981 September 13 (Box 94:73)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1982 (Box 94:74)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1983 (Box 94:75)
  - Fairfield University exhibit, correspondence, program, 1983 February 27 (Box 94:76)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1984 (Box 94:77)
  - "And Peace Attend Thee" exhibit, correspondence, receipts, 1984 (Box 94:78)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1985 (Box 94:79)
  - Atria Gallery exhibit, correspondence, invitation, 1985 October 15 (Box 94:80)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1986 (Box 94:81)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1987 (Box 94:82)
  - New Britain Youth Museum, correspondence, 1987 February 10 (Box 94:83)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1988 (Box 94:84)
  - "Poetic Images"exhibit, correspondence, 1988 (Box 94:85)
  - Hurlbutt Gallery exhibit, pamphlet, correspondence, 1988 December 10 (Box 94:86)
  - "The Illustrator's Art", correspondence, invitation, 1988 October 22 (Box 94:87)
  - The Lion & the Lamb Peace Arts Center, correspondence, 1988 February 20 (Box 94:88)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1989 (Box 94:89)
  - Marketing pamphlets, programs, for exhibits, 1990 (Box 94:90)
  - Rowayton Arts Center "Studio Tour", map, etc., 1991 April 27 (Box 94:91)
  - Society of Illustrator's, poster, advertisements, 1991 May 22 (Box 94:92)
  - "The Fantasy Makers", The Westport Arts Center, flyer, 1991 September 20 (Box 94:93)
  - "Monsters in Fact and Fiction", flyer, 1991 November 3 (Box 94:94)
  - "The First Fifty Years" UCONN, program, 1991 November 4 (Box 94:95)
  - "The Original Art", Society of Illustrators, invitation, 1991 November 12 (Box 94:96)
  - "Leaving the World Behind", invitation, 1993 January 2 (Box 94:97)
  - "Wide World of Illustration", invitation, background information, 1993 July 8 (Box 94:98)
  - Zimmerli Art Museum, program, correspondence, 1993 September 28 (Box 94:99)
  - "The Original Art", correspondence, invitation, etc., 1993 October (Box 94:100)
  - "Reflections of Nature", invitation, 1993 October (Box 94:101)
  - Bedford Middle School, new acquisitions listing, 1993 October 1 (Box 94:102)
  - H. Pelham Curtis Gallery, announcement, 1994 December 4 (Box 94:103)
  - Nathan D. Rosen Art Gallery, program, advertisements, etc., 1994 January 9 (Box 94:104)
  - "Happily Ever After", advertisement, 1994 February 13 (Box 94:105)
  - "Scenes of Westport", invitation, program, 1994 May 1 (Box 94:106)
  - "A Gala Evening Among Friends", UCONN, appearance, 1994 June 1 (Box 94:107)
  - Appearance: Society of Illustrators Dinner, invitation, 1995 January 19 (Box 94:108)
  - Norman Stevens Gallery, UCONN, invitation, 1995 March 26 (Box 94:109)
  - Westport Arts Center, invitation, program, bulletin, 1995 September 1 (Box 94:110)
  - "Meet the Press", invitation, 1995 December 7 (Box 94:111)
  - "Benefit Gala" program, correspondence, 1995 May 6 (Box 94:112)
  - Society of Illustrators, program, 1996 December (Box 94:113)
  - Westport Arts Center, flyer, 1996 June 14 (Box 94:114)
  - Exhibit Programs, 1997 (Box 94:115)
  - Art Exhibit Programs, 1998-1999 (Box 94:115A)
  - Interviews
    - Follett Library Book Company v.4, #1, 1981 Fall (Box 95:116)
    - Phone interview, 1986 July 8 (Box 95:117)
    - With Gail Olson- computer print-out, 1988 July 30 (Box 95:118)
    - With Stephanie Zvirin, 1993 November 15 (Box 95:119)
    - With Irvy Gilberston (schedule only), undated (Box 95:120)
    - Bank Street College Radio (schedule only), undated (Box 95:121)
    - With Billie M. Levy (flyer only), undated (Box 95:122)
  - Awards
    - Acknowledgement - for a book (unknown), 1970 (Box 95:123)
    - "Reaching for Excellence" Medal, undated (Box 95:124)
    - The Washington Post Children's Book Guild award, 1989 November 18 (Box 95:125)
    - "William Franklin Memorial Award" booklist, 1983 (Box 95:126)
    - The 33rd Annual Regina Medal Award, program, 1991 April 2 (Box 95:127)
    - Certificate of Appreciation from Special Olympics, 1995 July 1 (Box 95:128)
  - Articles on LEF
    - Something About the Author, v.34, pp.87-97, undated (Box 95:129)
    - "The Creed and Craft of LEF", undated (Box 95:130)
    - On LEF, magazine unknown, undated (Box 95:131)
    - Paper on LEF by Bernice Cooper, undated (Box 95:132)
    - American Artist / Metropolitan, 1969 March (Box 95:133)
    - Tabco Dispatch, 1969 March (Box 95:134)
    - Galleryscope, blurb on LEF, 1970 (Box 95:135)
    - Brooklyn Public Library Bulletin, 1970 May (Box 95:136)
    - The Crier, blurb on LEF, 1971 April 13 (Box 95:137)
    - Catholic Library World, "My Life in the Arts", 1971 Huly/August (Box 95:138)
    - Something About the Author, 1973 (Box 95:139)
    - "Godspell" play with forward by LEF, 1973 (Box 95:140)
    - Bridgeport Post, paragraph on LEF, 1974 May 5 (Box 95:141)
    - Articles announcing Silver Medallion Award Recipient, 1979 (Box 95:142)
    - Something About the Author, 1985? (Box 95:143)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, article on LEF, 1989 Fall (Box 95:144)
    - C & RL News, article on LEF's donation to UCONN, 1987 December (Box 95:145)
    - Wilson Library Bulletin, article on LEF's donation, 1989 December (Box 95:146)
    - University of Northern Iowa "Extending the Message...", 1987 (Box 95:147)
    - Journal of Reading, "Extending the Message...", 1991 March (Box 95:148)
    - Paper on LEF by Elaine Clark, 1991 May (Box 95:149)
    - Success, v. 4, #2, 1986 June (Box 95:150)
    - Children's Literature in the Elementary School, (pp. of book), 1987 (Box 95:151)
    - Childrens Book Collecting, by Carolyn Clugston Michaels, 1993 (Box 95:152)
    - Journal of Youth Services in Libraries, v.7, n.3, p.328, 1994 Spring (Box 95:153)
  - Essays
    - "Notes o the Invasion of Japan", undated (Box 95:154)
    - "History as Seen Through the Eyes of an Artist", undated (Box 95:155)
    - "A Painter's Notes on Contemporary Criticism", undated (Box 95:156)
    - Exposition: unknown title, based upon Exodus (from Bible), undated (Box 95:157)
    - On painting "Give us our Land", 1946 November 4 (Box 95:158)
    - "Figures of Fantasy" Thesis paper, 1950 May (Box 95:159)
    - "Magic and Other Realism", 1977 (Box 95:160)
    - "Ways of the Western Painters", 1979 (Box 95:161)
    - "Leonard Everett Fisher: An Autobiographical Essay", 1985 (Box 95:162)
    - "Leonard Everett Fisher..." photocopy with bibliography, 1985 (Box 95:163)
    - "A Summary Review of the Positions of the Westport...", 1986-1988 (Box 95:164)
    - "Finding the Narrative Voice", 1987 (Box 95:165)
    - "On the Fiction of Nonfiction", 1988 (Box 95:166)
    - "Historical Nonfiction for Young Readers: A...", 1990 (Box 95:167)
    - Excerpt from Diary, 1995 January 4 (Box 95:168)
    - "Creative Connections", 1998 February (Box 95:169)
    - "The Hindenberg", 1996 (Box 95:169A)
  - Posters, Pamphlets, Writings on Paintings
    - B'nai B'rith Calendar, cover illustration by LEF, 1962-1963 (Box 96:170)
    - A Horn Book Calendar, August illustration, 1976 (Box 96:171)
    - 200 Years of Progress in America Calendar, 1976 (Box 96:172)
    - "Six Artists Paint Still Life", notes and sketches, undated (Box 96:173)
    - Writings about paintings done by LEF, undated (Box 96:174)
    - "God in Man" painting series proposal, undated (Box 96:175)
    - "Lament" description, undated (Box 96:176)
    - Auction of "Sea Songs", undated (Box 96:177)
    - Auction of "Compositions", 1969 (Box 96:178)
    - Auction of "Spectators and American Lament", 1969 (Box 96:179)
    - Auction of "Floating Sphere", 1970 (Box 96:180)
    - Auction of "All Through the Night", 1994 (Box 96:181)
    - Marketing pamphlet: Colonial American Craftsmen Series, undated (Box 96:182)
    - Pamphlets featuring work of LEF, undated (Box 96:183)
    - Pamphlets illustrated by LEF, 1987+ (Box 96:184)
    - Pamphlets advertising LEF, undated (Box 96:185)
    - Poster: The Hartford School w/ photo of LEF, 1977 (Box 96:186)
    - Poster: Franklin Watts Historical Wall Map, undated (Box 96:187)
    - Poster: Our Reading Heritage: Literacy Map of the U.S., 1957 (Box 96:188)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Illustration plan and color specifications, undated (Box 96:189)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Sketches done with marker, undated (Box 96:190)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Sketches done with pen & marker, undated (Box 96:191)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 96:192)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Photo overlays, undated (Box 96:193)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Poster lay-out, undated (Box 96:194)
    - Poster: Bicentennial: Marketing Pamphlet, undated (Box 96:195)
    - Poster: Children's Book Council, National Book Week, undated (Box 96:196)
    - 2 Posters: Children's Book Council, National Book Week, 1960 November (Box 96:197)
    - 2 Posters: N.Y. Herald Tribune: Children's Spring Book, 1960 (Box 96:198)
    - 2 Posters: N.Y. Herald Tribune: Children's Spring Book, undated (Box 96:199)
    - Poster- miscellaneous, undated (Box 96:199A)
    - Poster: "Come to the Book Fair", undated (Box 96:200)
    - Poster: "Composers" illustration notes, undated (Box 96:201)
    - Poster: "Composers" specifications, undated (Box 96:202)
    - Poster: "Composers" sketches, undated (Box 96:203)
    - Poster: "Composers" sketches, undated (Box 96:204)
    - Poster: "Composers" Correspondence, 1975 (Box 96:205)
    - Poster: Westport Nursery School Children's Theatre Series, 1964-1965 (Box 96:206)
    - Poster: Westport Children's Theatre Series "Absolute Time", undated (Box 96:207)
    - Poster: "Statue of Liberty" notes and photo overlay, 1985 (Box 96:208)
  - Cricket Illustrations
    - Fugitives II, p.30 -scratchboard, 1979 (Box 97:208A)
    - Fugitives II, p.29 -scratchboard, 1979 (Box 97:208B)
    - Fire carriages, p.37 -scratchboard, 1981 (Box 97:208C)
    - Fire Carriages, p.42 -scratchboard, 1981 (Box 97:208D)
    - Contents page, Baltimore & Ohio R.R. -scratchboard, 1981 (Box 97:208E)
    - The Big Road, p.22 -scratchboard, 1981 (Box 97:208F)
    - The Big Road, -scratchboard, 1981 (Box 97:208G)
    - Innkeepers Boy, p.36 -scratchboard, 1988 (Box 97:208H)
    - Innkeepers Boy, p.41 -scratchboard, 1988 (Box 97:208I)
    - Innkeepers Boy, p.39 -scratchboard, 1988 (Box 97:208J)
    - Cry of the Conch, p.27 -scratchboard, 1983 June (Box 97:208K)
    - Cry of the Conch, p.29 -scratchboard, 1983 June (Box 97:208L)
    - Cry of the Conch, p.26 -scratchboard, 1983 June (Box 97:208M)
    - Nocturne for Late Summer -scratchboard, 1986 (Box 97:208N)
    - Whales in the Sky, p.61 -acrylic, 1989 (Box 97:208O)
    - Whales in the Sky, p.63 -acrylic, 1989 (Box 97:208P)
    - Whales in the Sky, p.60 -acrylic, 1989 (Box 97:208Q)
    - Hsieh T'iao Calm of Evening, p.4 -acrylic, 1990 (Box 97:208R)
    - Star Thief, p.25 -acrylic, undated (Box 97:208S)
    - Star Thief, p.24 -acrylic, undated (Box 97:208T)
    - Pen & ink Cricket on Empire State Building, undated (Box 97:208U)
    - Chinese Dragon, title page -acrylic, 1990 (Box 97:208V)
    - One for Plow, scratchboard, 1960 (Box 97:208W)
  - Illustrations
    - Stamps- (14) First Day of Issue, 1972-1977 (Box 98:209)
    - Stamps- news publications for, 1978-1980 (Box 98:209A)
    - Illustration of Statue of Liberty, undated (Box 98:210)
    - Illustration done by LEF, printed on milk carton, 1977 (Box 98:211)
    - Illustration- sketches for the University of Southern Mississippi, undated (Box 98:212)
    - Tear sheets featuring LEF's illustration, undated (Box 98:213)
    - Sketch notes for illustration for Saturday Review, undated (Box 98:214)
    - Illustrations for city of Seattle, undated (Box 98:215)
    - (Box 98:216)
    - Cut & paste illustration for Sydney and Anita Bernstein, 1960 (Box 98:217)
    - 100th Anniversary celebration illustration for congregation, 1962 (Box 98:218)
    - Cover illustration by LEF for Franklin Watts book listing, 1968 (Box 98:219)
    - Advertisement for the Colonial Americans, order form, 1969 (Box 98:220)
    - Illustrations- cover design by LEF, 1971 (Box 98:221)
    - Sketches and photocopy of scratchboard for Blair & Ketchum, 1980 January (Box 98:222)
    - Pen & ink design for Jewish Book Council, 1981 (Box 98:223)
    - Chalk sketch done at Westport Public Library, 1983 (Box 98:224)
    - Children's Book Council, cover illustration by LEF, 1986 (Box 98:225)
    - Illustration: "The Sun is Four Seasons", cut & paste, undated (Box 98:226)
    - Logos for USBBY (United States Board for Young People), 1994 February (Box 98:227)
    - Design for the Bridge to Understanding Award- USBBY, undated (Box 98:228)
    - 2 Prints from scratchboard illustration "balloons and stars", undated (Box 98:229)
    - Bookmarks (3 envelopes) of books and appearances, undated (Box 99:230)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, card specifications, undated (Box 99:231)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, designs and illustrations, undated (Box 99:232)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, designs and illustrations, undated (Box 99:233)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, color swatches, undated (Box 99:234)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, printed illustration, undated (Box 99:235)
    - Holiday cards- made by LEF, completed cards, undated (Box 99:236)
    - Hanukah cards- made by LEF, undated (Box 99:237)
    - Holiday cards- "Land of Promise", undated (Box 99:238)
  - Speeches/Eulogies
    - Eulogy for Richard's death, Temple Shalom, 1986 January 7 (Box 100:239)
    - Eulogy for Sanford's death, 1988 September (Box 100:240)
    - Eulogy for Deane Keller's death, 1992 May 13 (Box 100:241)
    - Eulogy for Steven Dohanos, 1994 July (Box 100:242)
    - Eulogy for Rudolph Franz Zallinger, 1995 (Box 100:243)
    - Eulogy for Myra Cohn Livingston and related documents, 1997 January 15 (Box 100:244)
    - Disc of LEF's speeches, undated (Box 100:245)
    - "The Artist at Work: Creating Nonfiction", undated (Box 100:246)
    - "All Through the Night", undated (Box 100:247)
    - Cleveland Art Institute, Ohio, 1961 November 16 (Box 100:248)
    - "Informational Books as Structures of Knowledge", 1962 July 31 (Box 100:249)
    - Washington Bookseller's Annual Dinner, Washington D.C., 1966 November 9 (Box 100:250)
    - "A Point of View", NJLA, 1967 September 21 (Box 100:251)
    - "A Point of View", NJLA, 2nd manuscript, 1967 September 21 (Box 100:252)
    - "Quality", RISLA, 1st manuscript, 1967 October 27 (Box 100:253)
    - "Quality", RSLA, 2nd manuscript, 1967 October 27 (Box 100:254)
    - "On Art and Design in Children's Books", 1st manuscript, 1967 November 28 (Box 100:255)
    - "On Art and Design in Children's Book's", 2nd manuscript, 1967 November 28 (Box 100:256)
    - "A Look at Life, Art and Children's Books", 1968 May 29 (Box 100:257)
    - Manuscript, C.W. Post College, 1968 October 8 (Box 100:258)
    - "My Life in the Arts", 2 copies of manuscript, 1971 April 13 (Box 100:259)
    - "Be Somebody's Something", commencement address, 1971 June 3 (Box 100:260)
    - "Men Who Create do not Destroy", NAEA, 1972 April 7 (Box 100:261)
    - "The Artist as an Author", 1st manuscript, 1973 October 13 (Box 100:262)
    - "The Artist as an Author", 2nd manuscript, 1973 October 13 (Box 100:263)
    - "The Artist as an Author", 3rd manuscript, 1973 October 13 (Box 100:264)
    - Manuscript, NEEMA, 1975 May 8 (Box 100:265)
    - "Bicentennial Remarks", 1st manuscript, 1975 October 25 (Box 100:266)
    - "Bicentennial Remarks", 2nd manuscript, 1975 October 25 (Box 100:267)
    - "Alone Among the Muses", Hartford Art School, 1976 March 2 (Box 100:268)
    - Cleveland Public Library, 1976 April 10 (Box 100:269)
    - Memorial Day Address, 1978 May 29 (Box 100:270)
    - 1st Meeting of the Westport Bicentennial Committee, 1974 July 17 (Box 100:271)
    - Quality of Life series #3, Staples High School, 1977 May 12 (Box 100:272)